I would’ve understood, Pops,
if she’d said it wasn’t possible.
But I wish she'd told me...
why it wasn't possible.
I didn't even get to explain to Estong
the real reason why I reacted that way.
She wants you to focus on yourself,
because she feels that you
haven't really gotten over your ex.
All I know is, from what
I read in Ysa’s diary...
is that you're still unsure
about what you want in life!
If that's all we can be,
then alright. We'll just be friends.
That way, you won't have
to avoid me anymore.
Better to be friends
than enemies, right, son?
Fair enough.
It's world peace for the both of you.
I'm sorry, Estong.
I can see the efforts you're making.
But I'm not the right personality
to make the decision for all of us.
Ysa...
I really love you.
Ysa?
I'm not Ysa! My name is Belle!
Ysa is just one of the personalities.
It's Belle. She's the real Ysabelle.
Ysa?
She's just one of the personalities?
How did that happen?
And— and how...
How would it be Belle?
I mean...
I didn’t even meet Belle until now.
Belle...
she's the first of them all.
She is the original.
Original?
She's Ysabelle.
You do know why her other personalities
come out, right?
Because she couldn’t handle
the trauma she went through.
A few days before she met you,
she experienced another one.
Do you like Estong?
You have to let it go.
We're only trying to avoid
what happened to you before.
You mean for Belle?
[parents screaming and fighting]
That if she gets triggered,
she might hurt herself again...
and us.
The Belle we know
retreats into her own world,
makes her own decisions,
and is very blunt.
And when she’s quiet,
you never know what’s
going through her mind.
- Belle!
- Belle, don't!
- Sweetheart.
- Belle, don't.
Belle, dear.
- Sweetheart.
- Belle, don't.
Sweetheart...
Dear, no!
Did you eat already?
One day,
- she met a guy.
- I'm done eating.
His name is Lorenz.
They talked constantly.
Almost everyday.
That was the first time
we saw her so happy.
We insisted that she meet
Lorenz in person,
so things could feel more
normal for her.
But after they met...
Dear,
are you okay?
Belle said
Lorenz was scared of her, so he left.
They never spoke to each other again.
Lorenz never reached out to her again.
Belle was hurt.
So she wanted to
forget she'd ever met him.
Belle isolated herself in
her room for a long time,
barely ever coming out.
Then one day, we were surprised.
Dear?
How are you feeling?
Belle is just resting, Nanang Barbs.
I'll be with you for now.
Um...
Who are you?
We haven’t met you before.
I'm Ysa.
It's okay, don't worry.
When Belle was last traumatized,
that’s when Ysa first emerged.
How...
How is Belle the original?
I don't understand.
Tita Barbs...
Estong, they're both completely different.
I still want to get to know...
Belle.
You don't understand.
Belle doesn't like her other personalities.
So whatever’s going on
between you and Ysabelle,
you need to stop.
I'm just afraid that
when she has to deal
with new emotions,
she might become even more confused.
We don’t know how this will affect her.
Another personality might emerge,
or Ysa might disappear instead.
I wonder how you're doing, Lorenz.
So...
You really like strange stories?
Mhm!
It's part of my job.
I'm a Junior Story Producer.
But,
can we not talk about work for now?
Uh...
I’m curious.
You’ve been painting
for a long time, right?
I don’t really have any other hobbies.
That's actually great.
Your paintings are beautiful.
But...
have you ever had a solo exhibit?
That's my dream.
That's why I'll put
together a collection first.
You can do it.
I know you can.
Thank you.
I hope...
more people will get to see your paintings.
And I hope...
your dream of having an exhibit comes true.
Just make sure you'll come, okay?
Of course.
That's a promise.
Uh...
Belle.
Is it okay if...
I hold your hand?
You're more beautiful in person, Belle.
You don’t seem hard to love.
Happy Birthday to you!
Wow!
Cake!
Wow! Yeye wants cake!
Happy Birthday!
Yay!
- Cake! You want cake?
- Belle. Belle, wait!
Cake! Cake!
- Belle, wait. Are you okay?
- Happy Birthday!
Why did you do that?!
Yeye wants cake!
Happy Birthday!
OMG! What's this?!
This is so sticky like ew! It's so gross!
Yuck!
Who are you?
What?
What am I doing here?
Are you my date?
Uh, miss?
Miss?
Excuse me.
- Were you the one who scared the kid?
- What?!
Let go of me! Why do you
keep on grabbing me?!
What’s your problem?!
You wanna fight?!
- What?!
- Calm down.
- What is happening to you, Miss?
- I said let go of me!
- What's going on with you?
- You keep on grabbing me!
Yeye scared of Kuya Guard!
I'm scared!
Guard, she's crazy.
Get her out of here!
- That's right.
- Yeah!
Oh, why are you guys
looking at me like that?
- Oh, don't look at me.
- Get her out of here, guard!
- Oh, I don't look so nice!
- She needs to leave.
Guard, let her out!
- Miss, you need to stop.
- She seems crazy.
I don't wanna be here.
I want to go home.
Miss.
My dears,
stop it.
Please, think of Belle.
My head hurts.
What's your problem?!
What?!
What are you looking at?!
What's your problem?
Why are you staring at me, huh?!
- Don't mess with me!
- Belle! Belle, stop it!
- Miss, miss, stop—
- Leave me alone!
- Belle! Belle! Belle!
- Knock it off!
- Belle, Belle.
- I said let go of me!
Belle!
Didn't I tell you to let go of me?!
You keep on grabbing me!
Base, we've got a crazy person here.
We need to call the police right away.
Just let me be, please!
Stop it now. Let me be!
Not now! Not here, not here!
Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
- Belle! Belle! Belle!
- My head hurts so much!
Belle!
Calm down.
Calm down, please.
He’s been there for a while now.
He hasn’t done anything.
Miss, what are you doing?!
You’re causing trouble.
- Get out of here!
- Guard!
Sir!
Don’t leave your companion behind.
But I want to see you again.
You promised you'd come to my exhibit.
Why’s that, Kuya? Huh?
Why's that? I don't understand.
Why did they only tell
you about Ate Belle now?
And Adel's just...
I'm losing it, Kuya.
Okay, that's enough—
And Adel's keeping secrets from me.
- Ugh, seriously!
- Shhh.
Sorry, sorry.
- Okay, enough. That's enough.
- I can't remove this.
- Enough!
- No, no, Popsy.
It's not right!
It's like they...they....
it's like they lied to us!
Right?
Oh, come on!
- Why?!
- Okay, stop!
You're being so
dramatic. It's not helping.
I'm shaking.
I'm shaking, Pops.
I'm serious.
It's wet!
Enough, enough, enough!
You know, Estong...
Ysa’s parents are right.
They're just protecting their daughter.
So if I were you...
if you can...
just stay away from Ysa.
Pops, I thought,
"As long as there's breath in us,
there's still some fight in us."
I won’t give up on her.
See?
See, Kuya? It’s also your
fault you keep getting hurt.
I believe that...
if I became close with Ysa,
I can do the same with Belle.
But they're not the same, okay?
They're both different personalities.
Their Nanang even said that...
Belle still isn’t okay.
What, do you want to confuse Ysa again?
Son...
You also need to protect yourself.
And your heart too.
Uh, hide that.
Hide all of it.
She can’t see that
and find out that her life has changed,
okay?
Because of Ysa,
the exhibit,
Estong...
Oh, all of it!
Doc, Ate Belle doesn’t know
she’s been gone this long?
Obviously.
Let’s just say she’s been hibernating in
her inner world.
But we’ll tell her
if she wants to know.
Just at the right time.
Uh, Doc,
do you think she’s recovering,
or is she still the same?
I can’t say for sure.
I need to assess her
first before we can know.
But what’s important now is that
we have to be very careful with her,
because she could snap at any moment.
The best thing we can really do...
is to shower her with
love and understanding.
That's what will help her.
- That’s what we should do.
- Exactly.
It's Belle.
Huh.
Why did you all suddenly go quiet?
Were you talking about me?
- No.
- No. Of course, not.
- No. No, sweetheart.
- No, Ate Belle, I promise. we weren’t.
- We weren't, right?
- No, we really weren't talking about you.
Why are you all trying hard to pretend?
I wouldn't be mad if you guys were.
What's that?
Oh, it's nothing.
Just put it down here.
Um, sweetheart?
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Hello, Belle!
You look good this morning. Right?
Right. How are you, dear?
You've been gone for quite some time.
Uh, Erna, she was just asleep.
She had a good night's sleep.
Uh, sweetheart, are you...
are you going somewhere?
I just need to finish my painting.
It seems like one is
missing. Have you seen it?
Uh...
Oh, maybe it just got misplaced...
Uh... don’t worry. I’ll look for it.
No, it's okay.
I'll just paint a new one.
I also need to talk to Ms. Amara.
She might be getting upset.
I wasn’t able to submit my work on time.
It’s so weird.
It feels like I’ve been asleep for so long.
How many days was it?
Oh.
Belle...
Don’t forget to take your medication,
and let's keep up with our
therapy sessions, okay?
Oh, Doc, didn't see you there.
Yeah.
You look like you’ve gotten fat.
Are you stressed? Are you stress eating?
Yeah. You noticed?
Mhm.
I'll get going now.
Okay, sweetheart.
Oh, God, I hope she's going to be okay.
I still have a tracker on Ate.
I'll see to it.
Okay.
Did I get fat?
A little bit.
I knew it. She noticed.
OMG.
Ysa looks so different today.
Looks like she's been through something.
- Excuse me.
- Ah, yes?
Two Americano Lattes,
one Iced Mocha.
All large. Dine-in.
There's an Americano Latte?
Uh, sorry, what was that again?
I said,
two Cafe Lattes,
one Iced Mocha.
All large.
- Dine-in
- Uh, hold on, there's a...
There's an error in the system.
Sorry, what was that again?
Forget it! close down!
Here, here. Look at this.
I just read this online.
- People online said it's good.
- What do they have that’s good here?
Let's see. I'll also check their...
- recommendations.
- Here are our best sellers.
Let's see.
Here we can see their reviews online.
I'd like to order.
Miss...
- there's a line. We got here first.
- We were here before you.
Why? Do you already know what you
want to order?
Not yet, but—
- Not yet, right? So I’ll go first.
- We were here first.
Ysa.
Oh, I mean Belle.
You?
You know me?
You’re the one who almost kissed me, right?
You’re also the one who slapped me hard.
How are you?
Who are you again?
Estong.
I'm Ysa's friend.
Ysa?
Yes, Ysa. One of the—
Do you think I care?
That's not why I came here.
Why are you here now?
This is a coffee shop, right?
What do you think people
do at a coffee shop?
I know.
You're gonna order a coffee.
Large Americano. Hot.
Just one.
Sugar level?
I don't like sweet drinks.
Oh, look, we're up.
- Hey.
- Hi, hi!
- Uh...
- Hi.
What can you recommend?
- Uh, actually, what's this?
- Oh, matcha for me
- Matcha?
- Kuya...
Let’s just pretend
I didn’t see you embarrass yourself.
She’s completely different from Ysa, bro.
You know, Kuya, I just
thought of something.
Why...
Why don’t you find a way
to bring Ate Ysa out?
What are her triggers?
Right?
Spanish Latte for Ms. Ysa.
Cold with 75 percent sugar.
Mmm!
It’s delicious! The flavor is just right.
Thank you.
- Mister? Hello? Mister?
- I know what to do.
Hello?
Oh.
We're going to order now. Um...
All of this.
- Uh, all of it?
- Yes, they look delicious. Yes.
I'm kidding. I don't have the budget.
- So, just a matcha and a latte.
- You can't afford them after all.
What's your...
what's your final order, sir?
Uh, wait, was that your ex?
Right?
- Were you guys a thing?
- No.
Good thing you two broke up.
Yeah, she's got attitude, right?
I wonder how he's doing.
Here's your order, ma'am.
So all of you really like painting, huh?
Ysa would love that.
That’s your shared dream, right?
You two were together last night, right?
What’s going on between you two?
Uh...
Ysa and I are friends.
Really good friends.
And your other personalities, too.
So I hope
we can be friends too, Belle.
Friends? That close?
You can do that with Ysa.
But not with me.
And let me make one thing clear...
just because you're
friends with my personalities,
doesn't mean you're friends with me.
Just leave me alone.
And the coffee isn’t even good.
That’s not the way I told you to make it.
I’ll have it replaced. I’m sorry.
Psst.
Hey.
So you’ve been keeping secrets from
my Kuya and me.
And
you’re always here because...
you want to see me?
- Excuse me?
- Nice one!
I never said I wanted to see you.
I’m here because Ate Belle is here.
Ouch.
Wait a minute.
Why are you guys always watching Ate Belle?
And you’ve even got a tracker on her.
Is that how it is now?
Ate’s tracker number has always been there.
So if anything happens,
we’ll know where to look for her.
Uh...
What could happen to her?
- Hey, Kuya Estong!
- Kuya.
I have something to tell you.
It’s from Dr. Wanda.
Um...
She said we shouldn’t just tell Ate Belle
everything that happened.
Why are you only telling me now?
Why?
Did you already say something?
I only said
I became friends with her personalities.
Are you sure that's all you said?
What else am I not supposed to say?
Uh...
Just don’t tell her what
happened last month,
what the other personalities did,
and... uh, especially about
you being with Ate Ysa.
Don’t.
What will happen if she finds out?
If Ate Ysa wants all her
personalities to come together...
Ate Belle doesn’t.
She wants them gone.
Because she feels like
they’re stealing the life
that only belongs to her.
Tita Barbs already told me about this.
It’s only just sinking in that...
Belle really hates them that much.
Alright.
You helped us with
the exhibit before, right?
Now...
I want to be the one to help you.
Alright, but no taking it back, okay?
Like this!
Ysa...
I really love you.
I miss you, Ysa.
You really won’t be able
to focus like that, Kuya.
You know, you’re always
messing with me, huh?
How am I messing with you?
I'm just trying to help you.
Whatever, bro.
Leave me alone, bro.
Just leave, I'm reviewing here.
There’s already a way to...
bring Ate Ysa out.
But...
it’s okay if you don’t want to know.
I'll just leave.
Hey, wait!
Don't be so sensitive, bro.
Nevermind.
- Hey, come on. Hold on.
- Don't bother.
Come on, what is it? What is it?
I don't want to.
Forget it.
Do you want me to clean your room?
I'll take care of it.
No, Kuya.
It’s already clean. I don’t want to.
Uh... food. Do you want
anything to eat, bro?
Whatever it is, I'll buy it for you.
I'm on a diet, Kuya.
You're on a diet?
Uh, hey.
How about money, bro?
I'll give you money.
What?
Just tell me, bro.
How much?
Spill it to me first.
How much will you give me?
Come on, just tell me first.
Okay, okay.
I thought...
What if...
you bring out all of her
other personalities first?
Then,
ask each of them
to help you bring Ate Ysa out.
I already thought of that, bro.
Don't you have anything new?
But...
you have to make sure
Ate Belle doesn't notice.
She’ll avoid you even
more if she finds out.
It’ll only make things harder for you.
Bro, I don't like Belle either.
If it were up to me, I
would also avoid her.
Kuya, there’s nothing you can do.
It’s her body.
You got any other ideas?
What else did you come up with?
Which...
of her personalities...
is the easiest
to trigger?
Balloon!
Yeye wants the big one.
- Big balloon please!
- Here's a big one.
Play!
Play! Play!
Yeye, but...
I don’t even know where Belle usually goes.
Kuya, I know.
Adel told me.
So you knew all along.
Where?
How much?
Here.
Where?
This isn't enough.
No, wait. Here, here, here's another.
- Stop pulling me.
- It's just money, okay?
Here. That's all there is.
Girl, if you want him to come back...
show them that you’ve already moved on.
How?
Post something on social media.
Pretend you’re with another guy.
Let’s see if he doesn’t come back to you.
Okay, I'll try.
Alright.
Bye!
Balloons!
Balloons for sale!
For everybody, for
birthdays, for every kid, and...
for those kids at heart!
It's our cousin's birthday,
we want to buy one.
Please, just one, mister.
- I'm not selling these. Leave.
- We have money to buy.
- Leave. These are not for sale, so leave.
- Mister, just one, please!
So rude!
Hello!
You want balloons?
Balloons!
- What am I supposed to do with that?
- Balloons!
Uh...the balloons are so pretty, look!
Beautiful balloons! Look how cute these
balloons are!
Like you!
Right?
Are you trying to talk like a baby?
Oh, wait. There’s one more. Just a second.
You want some prizes?
Look! Magic!
Don’t you...
don’t you love lollipops?
Lollipops are delicious, right?
Are you okay?
Also, I know you.
Are you following me?
I'm not following you, okay?
I just happened to be here too.
Besides, I didn’t know
you passed by here every day.
How would I know?
Oh, I see.
Don't follow me.
Oh, uh,
you wanna play instead?
You wanna play hopscotch?
One, two, three!
Or, uh, you want...
Wanna be best friends?
Pinky swear! Pinky swear! Pinky swear!
What's your problem?
I said,
don't follow me!
See mister, you got what
was coming to you!
Come on, mister, let
us buy your balloons!
We've been here for a while.
- Please, mister.
- You got reject—
Fine, fine. It’s your
cousin’s birthday, right?
Happy birthday to your cousin.
Here, take them.
Just go. Go on.
For free?
Thank you!
Are you sure they’ll pass by here, bro?
Kuya...
would Adel lie to me?
Kuya, Kuya.
They're here.
What? Do you have a plan?
Uh...
I'll just pretend like I'm
shopping for clothes.
I guess that'll do.
Shop— Kuya, is there anything else?
Something less predictable?
There’s a plot twist, bro. Trust me, okay?
I know what Cacai’s trigger is.
Uh...
Does this look good on me?
Bro?
See?
Look at the blue!
Mhm!
Look, the royal blue
with the "bling bling", right?
- Kuya.
- Why?
You're a shitty actor.
Just play along with me, okay?
Right? See!
- That one? Oh, Kuya.
- Yeah?
It doesn't suit you.
- Doesn't suit me? Tacky?
- It's tacky. Yes.
Yeah. It looks bad.
Oh, no!
You know what.
If only there was someone
who’s, you know...girly.
Someone who knows fashion.
That would really help.
Too bad!
- What a shame.
- I know.
Too bad.
I really don’t believe this
is a coincidence anymore.
Oh, you're here.
Was she here this whole time?
Uh...
We didn’t ask for your help.
Right?
Oh, is that so?
Mhm!
Too bad. I might’ve had an idea.
I was actually going to help you.
Aha!
- Kuya, Kuya, wait a minute.
- Yeah?
I just need to go there.
- Where?
- Just over there!
I saw someone beautiful.
Oh!
It's actually Adel!
Just a minute, Kuya.
Do you have...
any fashion tips for me?
Right?
Maybe something in...
brown?
Or maybe earthy tones, like...
navy brown?
That could work, or maybe something like...
neon black?
There, there, there. Get in there.
What is your Kuya doing?
He's just following his heart.
He's so cheesy.
Wasn't he already told he co—
He can.
Don't be so uptight, babe.
'Babe' your face!
Whoo!
What a dork.
I think...
I look like an idiot in this.
Exactly.
Ate Belle, wait!
Kuya, Kuya.
You're right.
You look like an iditot.
So, Kuya...
did you bring out Cacai? Huh?
There.
She's out.
Oh...
That was the plot twist.
Satisfied?
This one's for Aling Loring.
Yes.
Weigh it in.
- Did you weigh it properly?
- Yes.
How much was it?
I think it was a kilo and a half.
That's already enough.
Who the heck is this Estong?!
Why is he always following me?!
How close is he to Ysa?
And to my other personalities?!
How long was I actually
gone? How many days?!
What are you not telling me?!
Uh, sweetheart...
not just days,
but almost a month.
What?
A lot has happened while you were gone.
You finished
your painting.
You were included in the exhibit.
You were able to finish all of that
because of your personalities and Estong.
No.
That wasn’t me. I didn’t do any of that.
I didn’t do that.
Why did they even do that?
Uh, sweetheart.
Please don’t be mad at us for not telling
you right away, okay?
And also to your other
personalities like Ysa.
She just wanted to help.
I don't need help.
I don’t need anyone’s help,
especially not Estong’s!
I hope...
more people will get
to see your paintings.
And I hope...
your dream of having
an exhibit comes true.
Just make sure you'll come, okay?
Of course.
That's a promise.
If you want the man who left you
to come back...
show them that you’ve already moved on.
Post something on social media
and pretend you’re with another guy.
Let’s see if he doesn’t come back to you.
So that’s what you want, huh?
You just won’t stop. Fine...
I’ll give you exactly what you want.
Hey, Estong.
Can you get the—
Hello!
Oh, Pops! Pops.
What's the problem?
Uh, this week...
I was told to go to the
embassy, Pops, for my visa.
They said they need some clarification
on my requirements.
Then don't be nervous.
Not at all, Pops.
It's not like
a licensure exam.
And I'm sure I'll pass as long as...
it's surely legal and not a scam.
Hopefully.
Good.
So, is this...
a sure thing?
Nothing can stop you now?
That’s the thing, Pops.
I’ve been thinking about it too.
Uh... it’s just that...
the closer I get to her...
it seems like...
the farther she keeps pulling away from me.
Don’t worry about it. Just...
you know, if she’s meant for you...
she’ll come to you.
Kuya.
it's Ate Belle.
See? That was fast!
Well, go on.
Pops.
Just go.
- Yeah?
- Estong.
Belle.
- Is that you? Not a—
- It's me.
Uh...what are you doing here?
I just wanted to thank you...
for everything you've done.
They’ve already told me everything.
Thank you.
Really?
Uh...
It was nothing. Don't mention it.
Plus,
you helped me out too.
Can I order?
Uh...
Are you open?
Pops, we're already open, right?
Yeah, we've been open
since yesterday, actually.
Yes, Kuya. We're already open.
What do you want?
What do you recommend?
Oh, our recommendation?
Uh, this one.
Americano.
- We have Iced Latte,
- Wait, hold on.
Why does it feel like
the tide suddenly turned?
or just Latte.
Just let it go, Pops.
What matters is...
they seem to be okay now.
Fair enough.
So, yeah.
If you’re hungry, we’ve got pizza too.
If you want...
well, we also have
refreshments, Iced Lemon Tea.
That’s good, too.
There.
It's finished.
Here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
- I'll just put it here.
Can you take a picture of me?
Oh. Okay, okay.
- Right here.
- Where?
Okay.
One, two, three...Smile!
I don't smile for pictures.
Oh, okay. Alright.
- There.
- All good? Let me see.
All good.
Estong, let's take a selfie.
With me?
Yeah.
Don't you want to?
W-why me?
Uh...sure, okay.
- Come. Come here.
- I'm game.
Uh, wait. Hold on, I'll just...
Okay, let's do it.
Here.
You're too far. Come closer.
One more.
I'll post it.
My artwork with Estong. Smiley face.
Why would she post it?
Did you say something?
Uh...nothing, nothing.
Oh.
Add me, okay?
Oh, sure, sure.
Just accept my request, okay?
Loves?
- Yes?
- Loves, look at this.
Looks like Belle’s been
posting about Estong a lot lately.
You know what...
I really gotta hand it to Estong.
He really won't give up on her, huh?
He's something else.
I was able to answer
everything, Momsy Tita.
They said I'll just have to wait for
the email with my visa grant letter.
But sure, I’ll let you know
as soon as there’s any news.
Estong!
Belle.
Well, well.
You're all dressed up today.
Why?
Do I always look haggard?
Ah, hang on.
I’m gonna post you on my story.
Huh?
Why? Oh—
Wow! Look at you!
All dressed up! The outfit...
the shoes, the hair.
Uh, okay. That's enough. I'm embarrassed.
I'll post it.
You're so handsome.
Why are you posting it?
Why not?
You gave me your consent.
Did I?
I don’t think I did.
Oh, so you don't want to?
- Okay, delete it then.
- Oh, no. It's okay, it's fine.
- No, you can delete it.
- Don't. It's okay, just post it.
- All good?
- Yeah.
I’ll go ahead, okay?
Thanks! I still have to
take care of something.
Bye!
What was that?
I hope her five followers like my outfit.
You know...
I really thought you weren’t going to talk
to me anymore.
Because you're Belle.
You're really different from...
Belle?
I'm different because...
because of my condition?
Hey, I didn't say that.
What I was going to say was...
you're really different
from your personalities.
Especially from Ysa.
Estong, can you not?
Don’t mention them to me.
I'm me. Just me.
Okay.
You’ve been typing on that for a while now.
Who are you talking to?
Huh? Oh. No one,
just a friend.
A friend.
Do I know him?
Secret.
Ah!
Let's take a picture.
I'll send it to my friend.
Smile.
I thought you don't smile.
Come on, one more. Closer.
Smile!
Okay.
Come on, who is it?
It's nobody.
Alright.
I’ll let you have your way.
Just do the same for me.
With what?
A date.
A date?
What are you talking about?
Just a friendly date.
As friends.
You're so random.
Why?
What’s the problem? We’re friends.
Tita, Tito...
I was just...I just brought Belle home.
We can see that.
- Ah, Estong...
- Yes?
Um...
Just text me the details
of our friendly date, okay?
Really?
Mhm!
Okay, I’ll just text you the time,
the date...
and the place.
Bye!
- Nang, Nong, I'll head inside.
- Okay.
- Alright.
- Good night, dear.
Good night! Good night, Belle!
Good night!
Estong.
You really didn't stop, huh?
Tita...
What I mean is...
thank you
for never giving up.
Thank you for staying by Belle's side,
even after you learned the truth.
For being there for her and being such a
good friend to her.
I accept Belle.
Whoever she is...
and whoever they are.
Isn't that a song?
Alright, alright. You can go home now.
Take care.
Okay.
Alright, go ahead, go home now.
- Good night!
- Okay, good night! Good night.
Good night!
Take care!
Whoo!
Pops.
Wow.
- Right?
- Looking good.
Looks just like me, right?
My Kuya is so handsome.
He definitely got it from me.
- There’s just one thing missing, bro.
- What?
- Oops!
- There you go.
Wow!
- Strato smells even better.
- Right?
Even if you don’t shower for a whole
week, Kuya...
- You're right about that.
- you'll still smell good. Right?
You're right about that, bro.
- I know!
- I like it!
- You like it, bro?
- Yes!
Pops, what's wrong?
Is there a problem, Pops?
Um...
No, nothing.
Son,
don’t you find it strange
that Belle suddenly...
became nicer?
Is there something you want to say, Pops?
Yeah, Pops. What is it?
No. No, it's nothing. It's just that...
I don't know. I just have this feeling.
But...
Oh, don't worry about it.
Maybe I'm...
just excited for you.
Oh, Pops.
You're always nervous.
Pops...
it's just a friendly date, okay?
Kuya's not getting married yet.
Okay?
He might trigger her again...
and who knows which
identity will come out this time.
He's right, Kuya.
Just chill, okay?
You guys should be the one to chill.
Maybe you’re just overthinking it, Pops.
There's really no problem.
- Nothing is going to happen.
- Sorry, sorry.
- Just chill, Pops, okay?
- Yeah, I know.
Alright then.
I’ll go ahead. I might be late.
Okay, Kuya.
Popsy.
Pick her up, okay?
No. We’re meeting there.
Oh, there?
- Okay, okay.
- You can have this.
Popsy.
- Take care.
- Bye! Bye!
- Take care. Be safe.
- Alright, Kuya!
Hey.
Mhm.
Don't. Even.
Oi.
- Hey, Pops, look at that.
- Shhh.
Hey!
Knock it off.
You really want it? Here.
Smells good. What's it called, Pops?
"Strato."
Body spray.
It suits you.
'Cause you're an idiot.
Hi, sir. Excuse me.
Are you ready for your order?
I'm still waiting for someone, so...
water's fine for now.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you!
- Let's go.
- Mhm.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
I missed this place.
The food is great here!
Glad we came back.
- Yeah, exactly.
- Belle?
Estong!
What are you doing here?
Lorenz, this is Estong.
I know you, bro.
I know you too, bro.
I'm Lorenz, by the way.
Nang, what matters is
that Lorenz is back,
he’s here, and we’re okay now.
That's why, I’m glad…
because you’re embracing
everything you’re feeling right now.
You're accepting everything
that brings you both pain and happiness,
especially in love.
Belle, are you okay?
I'll call for help.
No need, Estong. I'm okay.
Ysa?
You're sure of what you heard...
so why don't you
tell Ate Belle already?
I can't bro.
She’ll get hurt. She might
hurt herself again,
and that’s not all…
Ysa might not be the only
one who’ll come out.
Then, that's what you need to tell her.
What, Pops?
Be straight with Belle.
Tell her you’re jealous and you’re
worried she’ll just end up with Lorenz.
I'm here to court you, Belle!